Yes, ok, thank you very much, but right now, I've got to dial China.
All right, so long.
Hi everyone.
My name is Russ Handler, and did you ever know that when you call an international number out of the United States, there's actually four separate numbers that you have to dial?
Pretty interesting, and a lot of numbers to keep straight.
Let's say you want to dial China.
Here's how you do it.
First of all, you'll dial 011, then that will get you out of the country.
Then of course, the next number, is going to be a country code, in this case for China, 86.
Then, you have a city code.
Let's say for instance, you're dialing Bejing.
That would be 10, then the number.
Pretty intricate amount of numbers that you need to know, and keep in mind, so dialing China, 011 gets you out of the country.
86 gets you into China.
Then, let's say you're dialing Bejing.
That would be 10 for the city code, then the number.
Let's say it's 5556321.
That's simple.
That's how you dial China.
Now, keep in mind if you saw the Olympics recently, they are the technological masters of the world.
Their infrastructure is 100 percent fiber optic.
They've got submarine cabling, and lots and lots and lots of satellite links as well, so you should have a great, clear call to China.
I'm Russ Handler.
Have a great day.
If you don't mind, I'm going to call Bejing.